a dying
described
A king
exactly
body so
eyewitness
an
it reads like
he
crucifixion
of a
account
saw.
never
twenty-two.
Psalm
it in the
wrote
David
person,
first
someone
describing
but he was
death,
else's
own.
his
not
of the
body
Watch the
man:
dying
like
out
"I am poured
water,
are
bones
and all my
of joint…"
out
Drained
loose,
joint pulled
and every
hangs
the way a body
the
suspended by
it's
when
arms.
And:
tell all my
may
"I
bones:
and stare upon
look
they
me."
bone,
every
He could count
exposed,
and
stretched
stared
stood and
onlookers
while
him.
at
crucifixion.
saw a
David never
not make it
would
Rome
centuries.
for
instrument
its
of
man
Yet the dying
marks
the
his song bears
early.
written
of one
bore
Jesus
This is what
every
home
to bring you
joint,
wrenched
stare,
every cold
so you'd
early
centuries
recorded
of it was
none
know
chance.
in your
crushed
He was
place.